Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. 16mm Microfilm As-Broadcast Scripts, 1928-1958
The John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- 16mm As-Broadcast Microfilm, 1928-1958
  - Eastman Kodak (Reel 1007)
    - Kodak Family Adventure
      - The Osbornes Look for a Home, undated
      - Osbornes Find a House, undated
      - The Little Green Bag, undated
      - The Trip to Cooperstown, undated
      - Teddy and the Modern Painting, undated
      - The Christman Story, undated
      - An Act of Congress, screenplay, undated
      - Little Red Schoolhouse, screenplay, undated
      - Indiana University Story, screenplay, undated
      - Teddy and the Magician, screenplay, undated
  - Swift & Co.
    - Swift's Movie Time, commercials, undated
  - Fanny Farmer Candies
    - Buffalo Billy, 1950 Oct.-1951 Jan.
  - Standard Brands
    - Tenderleaf Tea, Valiant Lady, 1956 June-Aug.
  - Sylvania
    - Beat the Clock, 1956 Jan.-June
  - Kraft Cheese
    - Kraft Television Theatre
      - The Battle for Wednesday, 1958 Jan. 1
      - The Velvet Trap, 1958 Jan. 8
      - Code of the Corner, 1958 Jan. 15
      - Eddie, (missing), 1958 Jan. 22
      - Run Joe Run, 1958 Jan. 29
      - The Spell of the Tigress, 1958 Feb. 5
      - Material Witness, 1958 Feb. 19
      - The Woman at High Hollow, 1958 Feb. 26
      - Dog in a Bush Tunnel, 1958 Mar. 5 (Reel 1008)
      - The Sea is Boiling Hot, 1958 Mar. 12
      - Look What's Going On, 1958 Mar. 19
      - Angry Angel, 1958 Mar. 26
      - Man in Authority, 1958 Apr. 2
      - Matinee Theatre
      - Modern Romances, 1958 Jan.-Feb.
      - Tic-Tac-Dough, 1958 Jan.-Feb.
      - Comedy Time, 1958 Jan.-Feb.
  - Brillo Manufacturing Company (Reel 1011)
    - TV Star Tonight
      - You Need Me, 1955 Feb. 3
        [Repeat of broadcast microfilmed on reel 1002]
      - Weekend, 1955 Feb. 10
      - Concerning Death, 1955 Feb. 17
      - How Beautiful with Shoes, 1955 Feb. 24
      - Zone of Quiet, 1955 Mar. 3
      - Ile (Eugene O'Neill), 1955 Mar. 10
      - The Murderer, 1955 Mar. 17
      - Matter of Life, 1955 Mar. 24
      - Death of a Stranger, 1955 Mar. 31
      - Treasure Trove, 1955 Apr. 7
      - The Lavender Kite, 1955 Apr. 14
      - The Giants' Stair, 1955 Apr. 21
      - Zero Hour, 1955 Apr. 28
      - The Dark Search, 1955 May 5
      - Second String, 1955 May 12
      - Tender Roots, 1955 May 19
      - Golden Victory, 1955 May 26
      - Taste, 1955 June 2
  - Sylvania
    - Beat the Clock, commercials, 1956 Mar. 10-June 16
      [Mar. 10 broadcast International Show; Mar. 31 broadcast April Fool's Show]
    - Syracuse show, 1956 May 3
    - Buffalo Christian Show, 1955
    - Beat the Clock, Atlantic City, undated
    - Beat the Clock, 1956 May 3
    - Beat the Clock, commercials, 1955 Sept. 24-1956 Mar. 3
      [Feb. 11 broadcast Gay '90s Show]
  - Kraft Cheese
    - Kraft Television Theatre
      - Night of Rain, 1957 Apr. 24
      - One Dark Night, 1957 Nov. 29
      - Country Music, undated
      - Divorcees Anonymous, undated
      - Portrait of a Citizen, undated
      - Material Witness, 1958 Feb. 4
      - Johnny Big, undated
      - Outline for a Television Play, 1957 July 9
      - Low Water at Hellgate, undated
      - Treatment for a Long Flight, undated
      - Look What's Going On, 1958 Mar. 19
      - I Woke Up Stupid, 1958 Jan. 15
      - Man in a Trance, undated
      - Accusation, 1957 Dec. 30
      - Amy, 1958 Feb. 12